Good morning, meeting for Monday, October 3rd, 2022, and we'll have the
invocation from our pastor, First Christian Church, Mr. Leon Mies.
I did ask for permission to pray for a few extras, and he told me he would tell me to shut up if it's a, do not, father, I thank you for our community.
And I thank you for the people represented here tonight.
People who risked their lives, works so hard, and I want you to keep them safe, watch over them.
Father, I, I just feel real burden for our fellow citizens in Florida.
And that's just going on and on for them.
Give them a little encouragement, and thank you for the people that are there, helping them.
Come for the ones who lost friends and family.
And, Father, thank you for protecting our community, the other night in Tulsa.
I ask that you bless that family that lost a boy and the one who's injured.
Father, I'm just thankful that we can lean on you and know that you take care of us.
And tonight, bless our leaders as they make decisions.
Let it be a meeting where they just sent you guiding them.
Jesus, name up, pray, amen.
We're the leaders of the United States of America.
And do the Republic for which it stands.
One nation, I know you're God, an individual with liberty and justice for all.
Four public input on schedule personal appearances.
Five consent agenda.
Staff recommends we provide them six and seven.
It'll be in the next one, correct?
Nobody signed up.
All right.
We've had a sign up there that said that we were supposed to sign up.
Fifteen minutes.
Don't find the meetings started.
Well, that's a bit.
Hold on.
Eight.
The tables are out to remain clean for principle.
It's already a relaxing thing.
The associated complaint proceedings to the amount of 1,264 dollars.
This is the most recent bill that we've received from them.
The majority of this bill was in relation to after we had done some press releases.
There were citizens' questions and both wanted their assistance in making sure that we answered the questions.
accurately and completely. So that's why they were engaged for for this and this is what the bill is for.
Please.
Yes, some of them came over. I believe that's where they all came from but I'm not positive on that.
But there were questions that were presented to the city that he felt is very important to me.
We have complete and accurate answers to those.
Not in whatever engagement with archived social archiving social media records in about a $299 dollar.
Evening everybody. So archived social is a company that will archive all of our social media posts and related comments because they are subject to open record requests.
Yearly that's going to cost us $35.88 which we have budgeted for but they were doing a half off special and then Melissa negotiated them down even more.
The $300 for the first year. We don't have to stick with them after the first year but it will make her life a lot easier if we have this if someone does a open records request she can export the results and search through them a lot faster.
And now that we have two people with the library doing social media.
Facebook posts and we have Melinda now so we have a lot of posts a lot more than we used to.
Bill, three hundred dollars for the whole year.
I'll make a motion to approve that.
Thanks guys.
All right.
10 any new business which is a reason since the posting of this agenda.
11 staff reports.
12 trusted community announcements.
13 adjournment.